slothster.com 2014-04-16

# Privacy Policy | Slothster

_Slothster Privacy Policy_

Date of Last Revision: March 1, 2011

This Privacy Policy describes Slothster's policies and procedures on the collection, use and disclosure of your information. Slothster receives your information through our various web sites, services and third-parties ("Services"). When using any of our Services you consent to the collection, transfer, manipulation, storage, disclosure and other uses of your information as described in this Privacy Policy. Irrespective of which country that you reside in or create information from, your information may be used by Slothster in the United States or any other country where Slothster operates.

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, please contact us via the "Contact Us" form located here.

 _Information Collection and Use_

**Information Collected Upon Registration:** When you create or update your Slothster account, you provide some personal information, such as your name, username, password, email address, and birthdate. Some of this information, for example, your name and username, is listed publicly on our Services, including on your profile page.

**Additional Information:** You may provide us with additional information to make public, such as a short biography, your location, or a picture. We may use your contact information to send you important notifications about our Services. If you email us, we may keep your message, email address and contact information to respond to your request. Providing the additional information described in this section is entirely optional.

**Additional Public Information:** Our Services are primarily designed to help you interact with Slothster Services and provide social interaction with other users from around the world. Most of the information you provide to us is information you are allowing us to make public. This includes not only the comments you leave on content and other profiles and the metadata provided when posting, such as the time and date of submission, but also the people you add as friends, the content you add as a favorite and many other bits of information. By default most of the information you provide is made public, however your email address, unless you explicitly share it, shall always remain private. Your public information is broadly and instantly disseminated. For example, comments you post on content are searchable by many search engines and are available to a wide range of users and services. You should be careful about all information that you share that will be made public by Slothster, since what you post may be viewed all around the world instantly.

**Log Data:** Our servers automatically record information ("Log Data") created by your use of the Services. Log Data may include information such as your IP address, browser type, the referring domain, pages visited, and search terms. Other actions, such as interactions with other members and Slothster content, may also be included in Log Data. Log Data is never disclosed to third parties and is used to analyze usage and continually improve our Services by ensuring all representative configurations are addressed.

**Cookies:** Like many websites, we use "cookie" technology to collect additional website usage data and to improve our Services, but we do not require cookies for many parts of our Services such as looking at public user profiles. A cookie is a small data file that is transferred to your computer's hard disk. Slothster may use both session cookies and persistent cookies to better understand how you interact with our Services, to monitor aggregate usage by our users and web traffic routing on our Services, and to improve our Services. We do use session cookies to confirm that you are logged into Slothster, and you can instruct your browser, by editing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit, however in some cases that may impact your ability to use Slothster. 

**Third Party Services:** Slothster uses a variety of services hosted by third parties to help provide our Services and to help us understand the use of our Services. These services may collect information sent by your browser as part of a web page request, such as cookies or your IP request, however we do not disclose your private information to these third party services except in the limited circumstances described below.

 _Information Sharing and Disclosure_

**Your Consent:** We may share or disclose your information with your consent, such as when you use a third party web client to access your Slothster account.

**Google Display Network:** Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on Slothster. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to Slothster and other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy located at [ http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/](http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/).

**Service Providers:** We engage certain trusted third parties to perform functions and provide services to us. We may share your personal information with these third parties, but only to the extent necessary to perform these functions and provide such services, and only pursuant to obligations mirroring the protections of this privacy policy.

**Law and Harm:** We may disclose your information if we believe that it is reasonably necessary to comply with a law, regulation or legal request; to protect the safety of any person; to address fraud, security or technical issues; or to protect Slothster's rights or property.

**Business Transfers:** In the event that Slothster is involved in a bankruptcy, merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets, your information may be sold or transferred as part of that transaction. The promises in this privacy policy will apply to your information as transferred to the new entity.

**Non-Private or Non-Personal Information:** We may share or disclose your non-private, aggregated or otherwise non-personal information, such as your comments on content or public profile information.

 _Modifying Your Personal Information_

If you are a registered user of our Services, we provide you with tools to access or modify the personal information you provided to us and associated with your account.

 _Our Policy Towards Children_

Our Services are not directed to people under 13. If you become aware that your child has provided us with personal information without your consent, please contact us as soon as possible using the Contact Us form by clicking here. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information, we take steps to remove such information and terminate the child's account.

 _Third party links_

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on Slothster. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies and it is highly recommended you review their privacy policies which may differ from ours. Due to the fact we do not operate or control these sites, we cannot bear responsibility or liability for the content, activities, or policies of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we do seek to protect the integrity of Slothster and welcome any feedback about these sites. Feedback can be submitted by using the "Contact Us" form linked  here for your convenience.

 _Changes to this Policy_

We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. The most current version of the policy will govern our use of your information and will always be at http://www.slothster.com/privacy. By continuing to access or use the Services after those changes become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy.
